EC2 missing:Application ù 0 found:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
* Missing Tag Audit Result:
  - Since the account contains 0 EC2 instances due to our serverless Fargate 
    architecture, there are no untagged or "forgotten" EC2 resources leaking 
    costs in the background.
  - All containerized microservices for the KicksShoes project are strictly managed 
    via ECS Task Definitions, where environment tags (such as Group=13 and 
    Application=KicksShoes) are controlled programmatically.