EC2 no filter ù 0 found:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------
* Why are there 0 EC2 instances found?
  - Group 13 deployed the KicksShoes system using Amazon ECS (Elastic Container Service) 
    with AWS Fargate as the launch type.
  - AWS Fargate is a serverless compute engine for containers. It eliminates the 
    need to provision, configure, or manage virtual machines (EC2 instances).
  - Therefore, running standard EC2-focused commands correctly returns 0 active 
    instances, validating that our environment is completely serverless and 
    highly optimized.